export const Data = {
    presentTense: [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "My parents  _____  near Chennai.",
        "Choices" : ["are living","will live","have lived","live"],
        "answer" : "live"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "I  _____  my parents twice a month.",
        "Choices" : ["visit","am visiting","have visited","will visit"],
        "answer" : "visit"
    },    
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What are you doing there? I _____ TV.",
        "Choices" : ["watch","am watching","have watched","will watch"],
        "answer" : "am watching"
    },    
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Watch carefully. First I _____ a cucumber and _____ it into small pieces.",
        "Choices" : ["am taking, am cutting","take, cut","am taking, cut","take, am cutting"],
        "answer" : "take, cut"
    },    
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "I will follow you wherever you _____ .",
        "Choices" : ["will go","are going","go","goes"],
        "answer" : "go"
    },    
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "I will call you if I _____ time.",
        "Choices" : ["get","am getting","have got","will get"],
        "answer" : "get"
    },    
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What _____ snakes _____ ?",
        "Choices" : ["do, eat","are, eating","are, eat","were, eating"],
        "answer" : "do, eat"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "How _____ I _____ to the airport?",
        "Choices" : ["do, get","am, getting","do, getting"],
        "answer" : "do, get"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "I _____ this fragrance very much.",
        "Choices" : ["like","am liking","have liked","will like"],
        "answer" : "like"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "I will hit anybody who _____ me names.",
        "Choices" : ["calls","is calling","has called","will call"],
        "answer" : "calls"
    },    
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Why _____ she _____ on the table?",
        "Choices" : ["does, stand","is, standing","does, standing","will stand"],
        "answer" : "is, standing"
    },    
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "The temple _____ on a hill outside the town.",
        "Choices" : ["is standing","has stood","stands","will stand"],
        "answer" : "stands"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Some teachers _____ much homework.",
        "Choices" : ["give","gives","are give","are give"],
        "answer" : "give"
    },
    {
        "id":14,
        "question": "Taylor and Adam _____ good friends.",
        "Choices" : ["be","is","are","does"],
        "answer" : "are"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "_____ your parents let you go to bed late?",
        "Choices" : ["Are","Does","Do","Is"],
        "answer" : "Do"
    },
],
    pastTense: [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Andrew _____ go to the cinema yesterday. He ____ at home.",
            "Choices" : ["wasn't / stayed","didn't / was stayed","wasn't / was stay","didn't / stayed"],
            "answer" : "didn't / stayed"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "She _____ cook anything so the children _____ hungry.",
            "Choices" : ["wasn't / were","wasn't / did","didn't / ate","didn't / were"],
            "answer" : "didn't / were"
        },    
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "There _____ an interesting movie on TV last night but I _____ watch it.",
            "Choices" : ["did / didn't","was / wasn't","was / didn't","did / wasn't"],
            "answer" : "was / didn't"
        },    
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "The door _____ open but the children _____ enter the room.",
            "Choices" : ["did / didn't, am cutting","was / weren't","was / didn't","did / weren't"],
            "answer" : "was / didn't"
        },    
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "The young man _____ two sandwiches but he ____ still hungry.",
            "Choices" : ["did eat / was","ate / was","eated / was","ate / did"],
            "answer" : "ate / was"
        },    
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "The police _____ the thief but they _____ find the jewellery.",
            "Choices" : ["catched / can't","caught / couldn't","caught / weren't","were catch / didn't"],
            "answer" : "caught / couldn't"
        },    
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "The firefighter _____ for the little boy in the rooms and he _____ him.",
            "Choices" : ["looked / found","was looked / was found","did look / did find","looked / was find"],
            "answer" : "looked / found"
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "He _____ buy anything to eat because he _____ his wallet.",
            "Choices" : ["didn't / lost","can't / lose","wasn't / lost", "didn't / was lose"],
            "answer" : "didn't / lost"
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "They _____ play football because there _____ enough players.",
            "Choices" : ["weren't / weren't","didn't / weren't","aren't / aren't","didn't / wasn't"],
            "answer" : "didn't / weren't"
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "The young lady _____ me a cup of tea but I _____ drink it because it _____ hot enough. I _____ it on the table.",
            "Choices" : ["brought / wasn't / wasn't / left","was bring / didn't / was / left","brought / didn't / wasn't / left","bring / didn't / wasn't / leave"],
            "answer" : "brought / didn't / wasn't / left"
        }, 
    ],
    simpleFuture: [
    {    "id": 1,
        "question": "People will _____ on the moon in the future.",
        "Choices" : ["be living","lives","live","be live"],
        "answer" : "live"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "I _____ return the book after I read it.",
        "Choices" : ["will","am","can","am going to"],
        "answer" : "will"
    },    
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Tom _____ at eight tomorrow morning.",
        "Choices" : ["will arrives","arrive","is going to arrive","will arrive"],
        "answer" : "will arrive"
    },    
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "When Tom arrives we _____ a party.",
        "Choices" : ["will has","are going to have","have","will have"],
        "answer" : "will have"
    },    
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "This letter is in French, and I don't know French. Can you help me? B: Sure, I _____ it for you.",
        "Choices" : ["am going to translate","won't translate","will translate","am translate"],
        "answer" : "will translate"
    },    
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Can you give Ann a message for me? B: Sure, Probably _____ him at the meeting this evening.",
        "Choices" : ["will see","am going to see","saw","am seeing"],
        "answer" : "will see"
    },    
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "I am not sure but It _____ tomorrow.",
        "Choices" : ["is going to rain","will rains","will going to rain","will rain"],
        "answer" : "will rain"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Nobody _______________ recognize you in that wig.",
        "Choices" : ["are going to","will","won't", "isn't go to"],
        "answer" : "will"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Choose the correct sentence.",
        "Choices" : ["He will comes tomorrow.","They will do it for me.","He will be at the meeting.","Where will you be yesterday?"],
        "answer" : "They will do it for me."
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "I will _____ right here until Jessica comes.",
        "Choices" : ["wait","be waiting","waits","not waiting"],
        "answer" : "wait"
    }, 
    ],
    presentContinuous: [
    {    "id": 1,
        "question": "I am _____ a sandwich now.",
        "Choices" : ["eats","eating","not eat","eat"],
        "answer" : "eating"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "I am busy right now. I _____ breakfast.",
        "Choices" : ["am have","have","having","am having"],
        "answer" : "am having"
    },    
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "My daughter _____ studying English at Istanbul University.",
        "Choices" : ["is","does","do","not"],
        "answer" : "is"
    },    
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "_____ you waiting for a bus?",
        "Choices" : ["Do","Are","Does","Is"],
        "answer" : "Are"
    },    
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What _____? It looks awful.",
        "Choices" : ["do you drinking","are you drink","are you drinking","does you drink"],
        "answer" : "are you drinking"
    },    
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "We _____ enjoying our holiday here so much.",
        "Choices" : ["don't","are","is","doesn't"],
        "answer" : "are"
    },    
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What _____ John _____ at the moment?",
        "Choices" : ["does / do","is / do","are / doing","is / doing"],
        "answer" : "is / doing"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "I _____ sitting down at the moment.",
        "Choices" : ["am not","will be","is", "don't"],
        "answer" : "am not"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Don't disturb him. He _____.",
        "Choices" : ["sleeps","is sleeping","is sleep","sleep"],
        "answer" : "is sleeping"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "They are _____ their coats.",
        "Choices" : ["not","put on","putting on","doesn't put"],
        "answer" : "putting on"
    }, 
    ],
    pastContinuous: [
    {    "id": 1,
        "question": "Yesterday, at six I _____ dinner.",
        "Choices" : ["was preparing","was prepare","was prepared","did prepare"],
        "answer" : "was preparing"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "My father ______ a novel while I _____ TV.",
        "Choices" : ["was read / was watching","was reading / was watching","read / watched","was reading / was watching"],
        "answer" : "was reading / was watching"
    },    
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "We _____ our school when he came in.",
        "Choices" : ["talked","were talking","were talked","talking"],
        "answer" : "were talking"
    },    
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "The kids _____ in the garden when it suddenly started to rain.",
        "Choices" : ["played","playing","were playing","was playing"],
        "answer" : "were playing"
    },    
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Most of the time we _____ in the park.",
        "Choices" : ["were sat","sitting","was sitting","were sitting"],
        "answer" : "were sitting"
    },    
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "While I _____ in my room, my sister left home.",
        "Choices" : ["was studying","studied","study","have studied"],
        "answer" : "was studying"
    },    
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "My baby brother _____ loudly so I couldn't do my homework.",
        "Choices" : ["was cried","cried","was crying","has cried"],
        "answer" : "was crying"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "The teacher tried to explain but they they _____.",
        "Choices" : ["were listening","weren't listening","listened", "have listened"],
        "answer" : "weren't listening"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "_____ you doing your homework at six o'clock last night?",
        "Choices" : ["Are","Have","Did","Were"],
        "answer" : "Were"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "The teacher was angry because some students _____ football in the class when he came in.",
        "Choices" : ["are playing","played","have played","were playing"],
        "answer" : "were playing"
    }, 
    ],
    presentPerfect : [
    {    "id": 1,
        "question": "I _____ my homework yet.",
        "Choices" : ["have finish","has finished","did finished","haven't finished"],
        "answer" : "haven't finished"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "My father is on the way. He _____ home yet.",
        "Choices" : ["haven't arrived","hasn't arrived","didn't arrived","arrived"],
        "answer" : "hasn't arrived"
    },    
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "I am not hungry. I have _____ eaten.",
        "Choices" : ["yet","now","just","ever"],
        "answer" : "just"
    },    
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "I have never _____ to Paris.",
        "Choices" : ["been","went","go","was"],
        "answer" : "been"
    },    
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "_____ you ever been to New York?",
        "Choices" : ["Are","Were","Do","Have"],
        "answer" : "Have"
    },    
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "I am still working. I haven't finished my work _____.",
        "Choices" : ["already","yet","still","never"],
        "answer" : "yet"
    },    
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "I am looking for my pen. I _____ it.",
        "Choices" : ["have lost","lost","did lost","was lost"],
        "answer" : "have lost"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "During the two years David _____ ten different jobs.",
        "Choices" : ["has has","has had","have had", "have has"],
        "answer" : "has had"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "I _____ a teacher since 2002.",
        "Choices" : ["was","have be","have been","had be"],
        "answer" : "have been"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "My friend _____ my new dress yet.",
        "Choices" : ["haven't seen","didn't see","hasn't see","hasn't seen"],
        "answer" : "hasn't seen"
    }, 
    ],
    pastPerfect : [
        {    "id": 1,
        "question": "I couldn't see the teacher because he _____ before I arrived the school.",
        "Choices" : ["had left","has left","left","was leaving"],
        "answer" : "had left"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "He was very tired because he _____ the bags upstairs.",
        "Choices" : ["have carried","had carried","carried","has carried"],
        "answer" : "had carried"
    },    
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "I was starving when I arrived home. I _____ anything for two days.",
        "Choices" : ["didn't eat","wasn't eaten","hadn't eaten","haven't eaten"],
        "answer" : "hadn't eaten"
    },    
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "He asked me to give his book back but I _____ it.",
        "Choices" : ["have lost","had lost","was lost","lost"],
        "answer" : "had lost"
    },    
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "The boy knocked the door. There was nobody inside. His mother _____ yet.",
        "Choices" : ["hasn't returned","haven't returned","hadn't returned","didn't return"],
        "answer" : "hadn't returned"
    },    
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "The sun was shining and the birds were singing when she got out. What a lovely day, she said to herself. She looked at her car but it was not there. Somebody _____ it.",
        "Choices" : ["has stolen","have stolen","had stolen","stole"],
        "answer" : "had stolen"
    },    
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "She answered all of the questions in the exam because she _____ very well.",
        "Choices" : ["was studied","had studied","has been studied","have studied"],
        "answer" : "had studied"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "It was sunny but very cold. The snow _____ yet.",
        "Choices" : ["hadn't completely melted","hasn't completely melted","haven't completely melted", "wasn't completely melted"],
        "answer" : "hadn't completely melted"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Clara looked out the window. The pavement was wet. It _____ at night.",
        "Choices" : ["has rained","have been rained","have rained","had rained"],
        "answer" : "had rained"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "He couldn't believe his eyes! His father _____ him a new laptop as a birthday gift.",
        "Choices" : ["bought","has bought","had bought","was bought"],
        "answer" : "had bought"
    }, 
    ],
    presentPerfectContinuous: [
        {    "id": 1,
        "question": "I _____ English for two hours. I am very tired.",
        "Choices" : ["have studying","study","am been studying","have been studying"],
        "answer" : "have been studying"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "How long _____ this watch?",
        "Choices" : ["have you been wearing","have you wear","are you wearing","did you wore"],
        "answer" : "have you been wearing"
    },    
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "The roads are closed because it _____ since yesterday.",
        "Choices" : ["was snowing","has been snowed","has been snowing","snows"],
        "answer" : "has been snowing"
    },    
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "William is my best friend. I _____ him for years.",
        "Choices" : ["have been knowing","have known","am knowing","have been known"],
        "answer" : "have known"
    },    
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "It is 7 p.m. and Alfred _____ yet. He _____ in the field since morning.",
        "Choices" : ["hasn't been returning / has been working","hasn't been returning / has worked","hasn't returned / has been working","hasn't returned / has worked"],
        "answer" : "hasn't returned / has been working"
    },    
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "You _____ piano for years but you still can't play a single song.",
        "Choices" : ["have been learning","learned","have learnt","have been learnt"],
        "answer" : "have been learning"
    },    
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "She _____ out through the window since she heard the bed news.",
        "Choices" : ["have been looking","has been looking","looks","has looked"],
        "answer" : "has been looking"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What a talkative man! He _____ since morning.",
        "Choices" : ["has been talking","has talked","is talking", "talks"],
        "answer" : "has been talking"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "The bus hasn't come yet. We _______________for an hour.",
        "Choices" : ["are waiting","have waited","have been waited","have been waiting"],
        "answer" : "have been waiting"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "My granny _____ my little sister for two days because my parents are on holiday.",
        "Choices" : ["looks after","has looked after","has been looking after","has been looked after"],
        "answer" : "has been looking after"
    }, 
    ],
    pastPerfectContinuous : [
    {    "id": 1,
        "question": "My dad _____ smoking in the garage.",
        "Choices" : ["has","had","had been","is"],
        "answer" : "had been"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "The printer _____ working well.",
        "Choices" : ["had not been","hadn't","had not","is"],
        "answer" : "had not been"
    },    
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Had the players _____ playing by the rules?",
        "Choices" : ["been","have","are","be"],
        "answer" : "been"
    },    
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "She _____ expecting the worst.",
        "Choices" : ["had","'d been","had being","is"],
        "answer" : "'d been"
    },    
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Had the teachers _____ before the strike?",
        "Choices" : ["been work","working","been working","been worked"],
        "answer" : "been working"
    },    
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Our pool pump _____ running properly before the storm.",
        "Choices" : ["had not have","hadn't been","hadn't being"],
        "answer" : "hadn't been"
    },    
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "My sister's roommate was upset. She _____ been waiting for an hour.",
        "Choices" : ["had","has","have"],
        "answer" : "had"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "I just heard about the accident. _____ been working all night?",
        "Choices" : ["Had the driver","Had the driving","Have the driver"],
        "answer" : "Had the driver"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "We were shocked to see her. _______ been expecting her.",
        "Choices" : ["We are","We have","We'd not"],
        "answer" : "We'd not"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "I finally reached my mom. ______ her all day.",
        "Choices" : ["I'd been calling","I have called","I called"],
        "answer" : "I'd been calling"
    },    
    ],
    futureContinuous : [
        {    "id": 1,
        "question": "They _____ when I arrive there at tomorrow night.",
        "Choices" : ["will be sleeping","will sleeping","slept","are going to sleep"],
        "answer" : "will be sleeping"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "David’s daughter is studying at secondary school now and she _____ at university when David is 55.",
        "Choices" : ["will studying","studies","has studied","will be studying"],
        "answer" : "will be studying"
    },    
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Next summer, when his wife and his children are on holiday, he _____ English.",
        "Choices" : ["will learn","was learning","will be learning","will have learning"],
        "answer" : "will be learning"
    },    
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Will you be _____ there when I arrive?",
        "Choices" : ["waited","waiting","wait","have waited"],
        "answer" : "'waiting"
    },    
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "The spring is coming. Migratory birds _____ after a month.?",
        "Choices" : ["will be returning","will be return","will returning","will have returning"],
        "answer" : "will be returning"
    },    
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "I’ll be busy all day tomorrow. When you have fun with your friends I _____ entire house.",
        "Choices" : ["will cleaned","clean","have been cleaning", "will be cleaning"],
        "answer" : "will be cleaning"
    },    
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "She is studying hard. I think she _____ in a few months.",
        "Choices" : ["is going to speaking","has been speaking","will be speaking", "will have spoken"],
        "answer" : "will be speaking"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "The engineers _____ on another project when you come here.",
        "Choices" : ["will working","will be working","will be worked", "will have worked"],
        "answer" : "will be working"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "She is planning to start her new book soon. Probably she _____ her book next month.",
        "Choices" : ["will write","is going to writing","will be writing", "will have writing"],
        "answer" : "will be writing"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Their parents _____ their house when they return home tomorrow..",
        "Choices" : ["will be painted","will have paint","have painted", "will be painting"],
        "answer" : "will be painting"
    },   
    ],
    futurePerfect : [
    {    "id": 1,
        "question": "I thought I _____ (forget) you by then.",
        "Choices" : ["will been forgotten","will have forget","will have been forget","will have forgotten"],
        "answer" : "will have forgotten"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "When you arrive, we _____ (leave) the house.",
        "Choices" : ["will have left","will be left","will be leaved","will have left"],
        "answer" : "will have left"
    },    
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "When you reach the airport, the plane _____ (arrive).",
        "Choices" : ["will have arrive","will be arrived","will have arrived","will been arrived"],
        "answer" : "will have arrived"
    },    
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "By the time he comes, we ______ (finish) with the meal.",
        "Choices" : ["will be finished","will have finished","will have been finished","will have finishing"],
        "answer" : "'will have finished"
    },    
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "She _____ (graduate) from this university by June..",
        "Choices" : ["will have been graduated","will been graduated","will have graduated","will be graduated"],
        "answer" : "will have graduated"
    },    
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "By the time she meets me, I _____ (own) all of her family business.",
        "Choices" : ["will been owned","will have been owned", "will be owned", "will have owned"],
        "answer" : "will have owned"
    },    
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "When she comes, he ______ (be married) already.",
        "Choices" : ["will have be married","will have married","will have been married", "will been married"],
        "answer" : "will have been married"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "In June next year, my parents ______ (be married) for 50 years.",
        "Choices" : ["will have been married","will been married","will have be married", "will have married"],
        "answer" : "will have been married"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "I ______ (work) by June this year. Then I will quit.",
        "Choices" : ["will be worked","will been worked","will had worked", "will have worked"],
        "answer" : "will have worked"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "The way she started, she ______ (read) all books from our library by the time the next school year starts.",
        "Choices" : ["will be read","will have been read","will have read", "will been read"],
        "answer" : "will have read"
    }, 
    ],
    futurePerfectContinuous : [
    {    "id": 1,
        "question": "My mom ______ for two days by the time I see her.",
        "Choices" : ["has been travelling","will have been travelling","will has been travelling"],
        "answer" : "will have been travelling"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "They'll be exhausted by dinner. They will have been _____ hockey for seven hours.",
        "Choices" : ["playing","played", "play"],
        "answer" : "playing"
    },    
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Will you ______ here for ten years by the time of the Christmas party?",
        "Choices" : ["have been worked","have to work","have been working"],
        "answer" : "have been working"
    },    
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "It's a 24-hour relay. They'll only have been ______ for half the time by 6pm.",
        "Choices" : ["ran","run","running"],
        "answer" : "running"
    },    
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "We _____ been waiting long.",
        "Choices" : ["will not have","have not will","will have not"],
        "answer" : "will not have"
    },    
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "I _____ working for two years.",
        "Choices" : ["willn't have been","won't have been", "not have been"],
        "answer" : "won't have been"
    },    
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Won't they ______ travelling for two weeks by then?",
        "Choices" : ["have been","had been","has been"],
        "answer" : "have been"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "The teachers will ______ for a month by the time the deal is made.",
        "Choices" : ["have been striking","will strike","will be striking"],
        "answer" : "have been striking"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "The films run all night. We ______ movies for six hours by the time the feature comes on.",
        "Choices" : ["watched","will have been watching","will watch"],
        "answer" : "will have been watching"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "She'll still be groggy. She _____ undergoing surgery for three hours.",
        "Choices" : ["will has been","will have been","will be have"],
        "answer" : "will have been"
    },       
    ]

}

export const randomQuestions = Data.presentTense.slice(0, 10).map((item, i) => {
        return {
            "id": i + 1,
            "question": item.question,
            "Choices" : item.Choices.map(answer => ({sort: Math.random(), value: answer})).sort((a,b) => a.sort - b.sort).map(obj => obj.value),
            "answer" : item.answer
        }
        
})
export const pastTenseQuestions = Data.pastTense.slice(0, 10).map((item, i) => {
    return {
        "id": i + 1,
        "question": item.question,
        "Choices" : item.Choices.map(answer => ({sort: Math.random(), value: answer})).sort((a,b) => a.sort - b.sort).map(obj => obj.value),
        "answer" : item.answer
    }
    
})
export const simpleFutureQuestions = Data.simpleFuture.slice(0, 10).map((item, i) => {
    return {
        "id": i + 1,
        "question": item.question,
        "Choices" : item.Choices.map(answer => ({sort: Math.random(), value: answer})).sort((a,b) => a.sort - b.sort).map(obj => obj.value),
        "answer" : item.answer
    }
    
})
export const presentContinuousQuestions = Data.presentContinuous.slice(0, 10).map((item, i) => {
    return {
        "id": i + 1,
        "question": item.question,
        "Choices" : item.Choices.map(answer => ({sort: Math.random(), value: answer})).sort((a,b) => a.sort - b.sort).map(obj => obj.value),
        "answer" : item.answer
    }
    
})
export const pastContinuousQuestions = Data.pastContinuous.slice(0, 10).map((item, i) => {
    return {
        "id": i + 1,
        "question": item.question,
        "Choices" : item.Choices.map(answer => ({sort: Math.random(), value: answer})).sort((a,b) => a.sort - b.sort).map(obj => obj.value),
        "answer" : item.answer
    }
    
})
export const presentPerfectQuestions = Data.presentPerfect.slice(0, 10).map((item, i) => {
    return {
        "id": i + 1,
        "question": item.question,
        "Choices" : item.Choices.map(answer => ({sort: Math.random(), value: answer})).sort((a,b) => a.sort - b.sort).map(obj => obj.value),
        "answer" : item.answer
    }
    
})
export const pastPerfectQuestions = Data.pastPerfect.slice(0, 10).map((item, i) => {
    return {
        "id": i + 1,
        "question": item.question,
        "Choices" : item.Choices.map(answer => ({sort: Math.random(), value: answer})).sort((a,b) => a.sort - b.sort).map(obj => obj.value),
        "answer" : item.answer
    }
    
})
export const presentPerfectContinuousQuestions = Data.presentPerfectContinuous.slice(0, 10).map((item, i) => {
    return {
        "id": i + 1,
        "question": item.question,
        "Choices" : item.Choices.map(answer => ({sort: Math.random(), value: answer})).sort((a,b) => a.sort - b.sort).map(obj => obj.value),
        "answer" : item.answer
    }
    
})
export const pastPerfectContinuousQuestions = Data.pastPerfectContinuous.slice(0, 10).map((item, i) => {
    return {
        "id": i + 1,
        "question": item.question,
        "Choices" : item.Choices.map(answer => ({sort: Math.random(), value: answer})).sort((a,b) => a.sort - b.sort).map(obj => obj.value),
        "answer" : item.answer
    }
    
})
export const futureContinuousQuestions = Data.futureContinuous.slice(0, 10).map((item, i) => {
    return {
        "id": i + 1,
        "question": item.question,
        "Choices" : item.Choices.map(answer => ({sort: Math.random(), value: answer})).sort((a,b) => a.sort - b.sort).map(obj => obj.value),
        "answer" : item.answer
    }
    
})
export const futurePerfectQuestions = Data.futurePerfect.slice(0, 10).map((item, i) => {
    return {
        "id": i + 1,
        "question": item.question,
        "Choices" : item.Choices.map(answer => ({sort: Math.random(), value: answer})).sort((a,b) => a.sort - b.sort).map(obj => obj.value),
        "answer" : item.answer
    }
    
})
export const futurePerfectContinuousQuestions = Data.futurePerfectContinuous.slice(0, 10).map((item, i) => {
    return {
        "id": i + 1,
        "question": item.question,
        "Choices" : item.Choices.map(answer => ({sort: Math.random(), value: answer})).sort((a,b) => a.sort - b.sort).map(obj => obj.value),
        "answer" : item.answer
    }
    
})